Wow, so this is how the autopilot works!
Isn't this awesome?
Don't go getting carried away now!
Didn't the book say there's a chance that
the helicopter can fall out of the sky?
Emporio.
It's further west. Head that way.
What do you mean?
If we keep heading in this direction,
and we'll make it to Cape
Canaveral in 30 minutes.
I can sense his presence.
I don't really understand why,
but it feels like he's in three
or four different locations.
For now, head west.
I'm positive the priest
is somewhere near Orlando.
You'll just have to trust me.
Something's not right.
Hermes, it's my eyes. There.
What the?
What's happening to my eyes?
They're closing by themselves!
Jolene, some weird shit's going on.
Damn it!
Now it's my eyelids!
I can't open them!
Hey, Hermes!
Did you see what happened?
What the hell is going on?
I don't know, but one thing's for sure.
There's something in this chopper with us!
Destiny is mine I don't know if all of
thread of lies I
don't know if I can't I
don't
know
if I can't
We'll
be
right back.
You need to get back in control
right now, Emporio! Yeah, I know!
I'm trying to put it on autopilot,
but I can't see anything!
We must be under attack
by an enemy's stand!
But still, what they do to us!
We're tilting way to the right!
Hurry up and straighten us out!
I'm trying!
My eyelids are glued shut
and they're not opening!
Something's definitely
on this thing with us!
Are you sure something's in here?
I've got my threads spread out
and nothing's even grazing them!
It's here!
It must have slipped
through a small window!
It just works out damn
fast and we can't feel it!
Why the hell is it attacking so quickly?
If only we knew where the
little shit was going!
So if we know where it's
headed, we can stop it.
We just gotta figure out which
direction it's going, right?
That's right!
There's no other way! Fine then.
Okay, Hermes.
How fast is this thing
going right now? 170? 200?
We're getting off of this thing! Emporio!
What the hell?
Choline, you idiot!
What were you thinking
pulling us out of there?
Look, it's coming!
I got you now.
Sayonara, sucker!
There it goes!
We crushed the little bastard!
Ah, shit!
There's more than just
one of these things!
Hang on, Armas! I've got you!
I won't let us hit the ground!
You okay, Emporio?
Yeah, my eyelids are back to normal.
I can see again.
What just happened to us?
Let's stay alert!
The enemy's attack is far from over.
I saw a lot more of them up there and
besides this thing ain't even a stand.
It's some kind of creature
What the hell am I looking at?
Don't know but maybe controlling these
creatures is the enemy stands ability.
Hold on.
Yeah, I think I've seen
one of these before
You know before this I could hardly do
anything for myself Not even drive a car.
But now, my ability to
concentrate is a whole lot better.
And attacking a helicopter
is child's play.
It must be him.
He's one of the entities
that I've been tracking.
Is he working for the priest?
Rikil, focus your mind
on the man named Dio.
Center yourself and think hard
about the bloodline you come from.
You're one of three sons who grew up
not knowing who your own father was.
Both of my eyelids.
I don't know why, but they
always droop down on me randomly.
It happens to me all the time.
At my checkups, the doctors claim that
there's nothing wrong with my body.
That's what they always
say and it's been happening
since I was 16 it all
started when I was taking
my final exams damn it it
was hard to breathe then
everyone around me was
staring say shit like oh poor
kid or just ignoring me
which just made me freak
out even more after that
I stopped going to school
and never went back my
eyes they're all fucked up
and I can't breathe oh man
I need to I wipe my palms,
they're drenched with sweat!
This kind of shit happens
every time I get stressed out!
Rikyo.
I don't have any abilities
that can help you!
I'm not capable of anything!
Wrong, you do have an ability.
You just haven't realized it yet, Rikyo.
Live rods, have you ever heard
of organisms by this name before?
In some regions, they're
also known as skyfish.
They are one of those
so-called unidentified species.
A group of skydivers say they
encounter them while exploring a hole,
but they have no proof.
Later, a TV camera crew
tried catching the rods,
but due to the remarkable
speed at which they travel,
capturing a physical form was impossible.
Given the fact that they're
untraceable to the naked eye,
the only way to document
them was via video camera.
So imagine my surprise,
that when I was studying your disc to
discover what abilities you may possess, Yes.
I learned that the rods reside
here in Florida as well.
Are those things what you're
talking about, Father?
The ones up there?
They're here!
I can see them!
Now that my eyes are
open, I can see clearly!
These organisms are under my control!
That's my ability, right?
So, they were always here.
Did they just touch me?
No, they never physically
touched me, but...
I think these rod things have
been surrounding me all along.
You need to leave right away, Rikiel.
Your stand is quite formidable.
I shall name it Sky Guy.
Research them well, the rod's
characteristics, and utilize them effectively.
Don't worry, I got it.
I feel alive again!
I'm no longer a loser, panting and
sticking my tongue out like a damn dog!
Rods?
Yeah.
And if these things really are rods,
it means that their strength
comes from what they eat.
These creatures are so mysterious,
no one has the slightest clue
what kind of food they feast on.
The unique way they fly without
ever touching anything must
have something to do with how
they hunt for their meals.
Stay here, Emporio.
We'll take care of this guy.
Yes, keep coming closer,
Jolene, Cujo, and Hermes.
With the Rod's precise attacks,
your bodies will be in tatters.
I just have to lure them over here.
Best not to get too close to him, Hermes.
Before that, we should learn
more about his ability.
Since he went through the trouble
of showing himself to us like this,
his stand's attacks must be a
lot more accurate at close range.
Yeah,
it was the jackass
attacked us while we were
cooped up in that chopper
with nowhere to go.
Which probably means his
attacks ain't so accurate
when there's a lot of
ground for them to cover.
Don't freak out.
The range of their stands are most
likely one to two meters at most.
So they can't take me out unless
they come closer to me anyway.
Shit, my bike!
I parked on a marsh, it's sinking!
I gotta start the engine
and get it out of there!
Where's the key?
It's not here!
They curved,
but it didn't look like he deflected
them in midair or did anything from here.
Yeah, I've got no clue how he's doing it.
But you know, Emporio, you'd be wrong
if you said those rocks didn't hit.
Let's give this jerk some more!
I can't fucking breathe!
And my eyelids, starting to twitch again.
I can see them, Hermes.
Flying in the air.
They're all over the place.
Now the rats are all suspended in mid-air.
This dumbass is panicking,
and now he can't even regain
control over his own damn ability.
Good job coming all the
way out here for us to beat
the shit out of you and send
you on your way to hell.
Die!
Found it.
The key was still in the
ignition this whole time!
What's wrong with my fingers?
It was july in the year of 1969,
when the astronaut
armstrong landed apollo 11?
and became the first man
to step foot on the moon.
The day was historical.
For the longest time,
I never understood what was so great
about some dude walking on a rock.
Because in reality, the rockets are launched
and flown by scientists and engineers.
Any monkey could go to
the moon but when those
rods came into my life for
the first time I finally
Realized why it was so
important it wasn't about
the dude the moon landing
was an achievement for
All humanity that day we
humans conquered the moon
and our spirits evolved
what's truly Significant
is the evolution of the
human race what the fuck
man my hand is rotting
My urine's all bloody!
For some reason, there's
bloody pee everywhere!
I can't feel my leg either!
What the hell did you do to
us, you slimy motherfucker?!
If you're trying to hinder the priest
from attaining his spiritual evolution,
my hatred will burn with the
intensity of a thousand suns!
And I'll use it to tear you all asunder!
Jolene Cujo, I'll kill all
three of you eventually,
but for now, you're at
the front of the line.
It's inside your body.
The only way your ankle could twist around
like that is if something
did it internally.
From inside of the body.
I see.
Now I'm beginning to
understand what's happening.
Jolene!
I figured out their secret!
The rod survived by feeding on body heat!
The blood in my urine means that
there was an attack to my kidney!
The kidney on this side's undamaged
thanks to your father's disc,
but the other side feels cold because
all my body heat got sucked out.
In the ghost room that I used to live in,
I read about something like this in
one of the books on the right shelf.
When you look at human
organs in a thermography,
the diseased part of the body's temperature
is much lower than the healthy areas.
If the heat in your
fingers were to be drained,
the joints would bend by themselves
and eventually start to rot.
Drain the heat from your
eyelids, your eyes will shut.
And if it's drained from your kidneys,
they malfunction and you pee blood.
So these rods,
in order to survive, they
feast on other organisms'
body heat and use it to fuel themselves.
They come near you, but never touch you.
And you don't realize that your body heat
was absorbed until you've been infected.
Yo, brat.
You're a smart little shit, aren't you?
You're exactly right,
but I didn't make you chuckle-fuck sick
so that you would perish from the disease.
It was to make sure you
couldn't move around,
so that I can finish you
with pinpoint precision.
It's a hard target to hit, but there's
one area where temperature loss is fatal.
The main motor and sensory
control center of the body.
It's known as the brain stem.
They'll snack on the first
cervical vertebra on your neck,
and they've locked onto their target.
Jolene, you have to get away from there!
Go under the water!
No, Emporio.
I need a lighter.
Give me your ghost lighter.
Hurry.
No way!
You can't be...
You don't gotta worry about me.
I honestly don't even feel it.
Compared to all the shit I've gone through
to get to the priest, This is nothing!
You crazy bitch!
If you're trying to test my spirit,
it's way stronger than yours!
Where should I aim?
What can I target?
Which part of her body can the rod
suck warmth out of to finish her off?
She did it!
That star birthmark.
I have no clue who you are,
but I'm willing to bet that if I want
to learn where the priest is hiding,
I can just pummel the
information out of you.
Center yourself and think hard
about the bloodline you come from.
That's it!
I won't hold back!
It's true.
If your entire body is engulfed in flames,
The rods don't know where to
absorb your body heat from.
However, if there's any way
that I'm going to overcome you,
I have to put myself in the same
situation so that I can understand where
your weaknesses are by feeling the
pain that you're feeling in this way.
My heart is like Apollo 11.
Jolene Kujo.
My spirit will surpass yours!
Hurry up and end this guy.
Jolene
What the hell are you doing?
The bastard with the boob window
is coming around behind you!
What's the matter, Jolene Kujo?
Can you not keep up with where I'm going?
After the flames overtook my body, I
located one spot that I could still target.
And that's the inside of your mouth,
which you had to open in
order to take a breath.
The hypothalamus, which happens
to be above the roof of the mouth,
is also connected to
nerves in the eye and as
you breathe the rods can
enter your mouth and sap
away your body heat from inside with your
hypothalamus now damaged I
made it so you would keep
seeing me in places
when I'm not even there
anymore except that I'm
the victor I've won my days
of having panic attacks are over with this
newfound confidence I'm
going to reclaim my life.
I am Apollo 11! Don't you see?
I don't have to use my eyes.
And if he's aiming his attacks
at the inside of my mouth,
then I don't need to breathe.
He knew to come after
us in the helicopter.
Just like how I sensed the presence
and location of the green baby.
And how the priest can sense
that I escaped from prison.
I'm gonna ask you who you are one more time
and what the priest is doing right now.
Then you're gonna tell me.
I didn't realize how determined she was.
Her persistence in wanting
to find the priest,
the will that she inherited from her father,
Jotaro Kujo, has awakened inside her.
She's like a completely different
person from the Jolene I met before!
Okay, I give. You beat me.
But in the end,
the one who's going to raise the priest up
towards his goal of
attaining heaven will be me,
Rikiel!
And in his name, I have infected
myself with disease using these rods!
I've numbed the nerves between my brain
and body, and now I feel nothing at all!
Whatever pain you inflict on
me now will be utterly useless!
I won't fall until I die!
We can attack at the same time!
Will you be able to finish
me off before I kill you?
Or will the rods suck out what life
you have left before you get a chance?
And your first cervical vertebrae
will be wide open after I've
finished putting out the fire on
your neck with my own two hands!
I'm gonna finish you here!
No rods! End her!
Watch out, Tully!
Oh shit!
No!
DOLENE!
She can't be.
You're still alive?
Damn it.
I used my hand to put out the fire on the
back of her neck to lower
her body temperature,
but instead, My plan
backfired, just my luck.
Now my hands gone numb,
and my fingers interfered with my
ability to absorb the body heat properly.
Ah, shit!
Cholene! Aw, yeah!
A girl's alive!
Was it on purpose?
Is that why you kept pummeling me
instead of taking my hands off your neck?
Or was it just a coincidence?
Just dumb luck.
I barely made it.
That's a sweet thing to say,
even though you're just saying it
because it's what I want to hear.
But is it the truth?
Tell me who the hell you are, and what
brought you into the priest's orbit.
Listen, I feel so satisfied.
Before I knew him, I
couldn't even drive a car.
But since the day we met,
my mind has been at ease.
The inner confidence the priest helped
me find filled the void within my soul.
Protecting the father is
my reason for existing.
He is currently going through a change.
His beliefs and the will of the man named
Dio are mixing and flowing into his body.
And it's that spectacle that's
attracting us all to father Pucci's side.
Everything we've done is to
guide the priest And raise
him up to his ultimate
destiny of attaining heaven.
Jolene Cujo, the same
could be said for you.
You're making your way to
Cape Canaveral merely to serve
the priest's desires.
I finally realized that.
You said it was dumb luck.
You admitted that you kept
punching my face without
removing my hands from
the back of your neck.
By coincidence, right?
I see now it doesn't
matter who the victor is.
I can't believe I couldn't see it before.
That kind of coincidence is exactly
what the priest is in search of.
The happenstances that aided you up
to this moment, that's what he wants.
Clearly, you have fate
backing you up in your corner.
Was it me, or was it always you?
I'm starting to believe the priest only
ever wanted someone with fate on their side.
Today has shown me the
strongest power in the world
definitely isn't something
that comes from a calculation.
We are drawn toward one
another through destiny.
And there's another man who's special.
He must be since the priest
took away his memories
and decided to keep him
alive in that prison.
Weather forecast.
If that guy up and decides he
wants to break out of prison,
it won't be because he's
trying to find where you are.
It'll be for the sole purpose of reuniting
with the priest for weather's fate.
By the time Father Poochie gets a new
star-shaped birthmark on his shoulder,
Weather Forecast will have received the
same exact birthmark on
his shoulder as well.
Because he happens to be the
priest's biological brother.
I've heard enough out of him!
You never should have
talked to this scumbag!
What about my poor sister?
That bastard Sports Maximum killed her and
he's the one who revived the Bone of Dio!
Are we supposed to
believe that was fate too?
I call bullshit!
Getting in Space Bastion
is the priest's destiny!
Let's go!
To Orlando!
That's where we'll find him hiding, right?
Was the fact that Jolene
didn't move Rikio's hands
from the back of her neck
really a coincidence?
Or was that calculated all along?
Whatever may have happened,
Jolene never spoke about it again.
Traffic law in Florida regarding
the riding of motorcycles
clearly states that if one
chooses to ride without a helmet,
they will not be subject
to fines or penalties,
which means if a rider wasn't wearing a
helmet and they perished in a fatal crash,
their freedom to make that
choice should be respected.
That freedom to choose
is crucial to humankind
since the prehistoric age
and even to this very day.
Thank you.